export default [
  {
    section: "Science",
    id: 1,
    question: "Which Of The Following  Acid Is  Present In Our Stomach?",
    options: [
      "Hydrochloric Acid",
     "Citric Acid",
      "Sulphuric Acid",
      "Nitric Acid"
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    section: "Science",
    id: 2,
    question: "Sound Can Travel Through Which Of The Following?",
    options: [
      "Solid",
     "Liquid",
      "Air",
      "All Of These"
    ],
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    section: "Science",
    id: 3,
    question: "Which Is The Smallest Mircobe In The World?",
    options: [
     "Virus",
     "Bacteria",
     "Protozoa",
     "Fungi"
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    section: "Technology",
    id: 4,
    question: "Which Technology Is Used In Cryptocurrencies?",
    options: [
      "Quantum computing",
     "Blockchain",
     "GPS",
     "RFID",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    section: "Technology",
    id: 5,
    question: "Which Of The Following Is Not An Operating System?",
    options: [
      "Android",
      "IOS",
     "Windows",
     "C",
    ],
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    section: "Others",
    id: 6,
    question: "For What Does 'S' Stands In 'STEM'?",
    options: [
     "Science",
     "Sincere",
      "Solo",
      "None Of The Above",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  
  {
    section: "Mathematics",
    id: 7,
    question: "Which One Of The Following Is The Value Of ùúã In Maths",
    options: [
      3.12,
      <>
        <sup>128</sup> &frasl; <sub>19</sub>
      </>,
      <>
        <sup>20</sup> &frasl; <sub>7</sub>
      </>,
      3.14,
    ],
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    section: "Mathematics",
    id: 8,
    question: "__________   is defined as the value that is repeatedly occurring in a given set",
    options: [
      "Mode",
     "Mean",
     "Median",
     "None Of The Above",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    section: "Others",
    id: 9,
    question: "For What Does 'E' Stands In 'STEM'?",
    options: [
     
    "Electronics",
     "Electron",
     "Engineering",
      "None Of The Above",
    ],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    section: "Mathematics",
    id: 10,
    question: "3D Form Of Sqaure Is",
    options: [
      "Cuboid",
      "Cube",
     "Sphere",
     "Prism",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
];
